http://www.mill-ride.com/privacy

More
Mill Ride Golf & Country Club
Privacy PolicyAt Mill Ride Golf Club, we take your privacy seriously and this privacy statement explains what personal data or information we collect from you and from people who visit our website and how we use it.Who are we?MRGC 2013 LTD (Trading as Mill Ride Golf Club), is a registered company (registration number - 08633094) our registered office address is Mill Ride Golf Club, Mill Ride, Ascot, Berkshire, SL5 8LT. For the purposes of Data Protection, MRGC 2013 LTD is a registered data controller (ICO registration number - ZA378410).What personal date or information do we collect?The personal information we collect may include your name, address, email address, IP address and information regarding what pages you access on this website and when.How do we collect data or information from you?Make an enquiry via our website or via the telephoneUse our websiteTake part in a prize draw or competitionVisit the Club as a golferWhen you choose to receive news, updates or press releasesEnquire about a job opportunityWork for or with the golf club including suppliers and employeesExchange business cards with a member of the golf clubHow is your information used?We collect your personal data or information to operate our golf club effectively and provide you with the best information on our products and services.We may use your information:To administer your golf club membershipTo answer enquiries that you make prior to any agreement or contract.To keep you informed about our services, our insight into golfing trends and best practice, and invites to events, if you have opted-in to receive these communications.To update you regarding bookings you may have at the ClubTo keep you informed of promotions and initiatives availableInvitation to Open competitions.Notifying you of your resultsTo process payment(s) for green fee visitorsTo process a job applicationTo fulfil our obligations as an employerTo provide benefits to you as an employeeTo record accidents and incidents that occur at the ClubTo maintain security of our office and IT infrastructureTo invoice you, and to track payments you make or payments made to youWe believe that all these purposes are justified on the basis of our legitimate interests in running and promoting the golf club, our contractual requirements to deliver the agreed membership services to you, and our legal obligations, both as a golf club and responsible employer.  If you would like to know more, please read below:MembersProspective MembersJob Applicants, Our Current and Former EmployeesBusiness Partners (e.g. professional golfer)SuppliersOpen Competition EntrantsGreen fee visitorsGolf Day and Event BookingsDetails of our processingType of Data HeldHow Data is HeldMembersName and contact information.Emergency contact details.Information and documents relating to the membership we are providing, including. communications with you.Billing and payment information and bank details.Member’s handicapUnder 18’s medical conditions requiring treatment.Data is stored in Intelligent Golf which is hosted in secure servers within the EEA https://www.intelligentgolf.co.uk/privacyData is stored in Mail Chimp which is hosted in the United Stateshttps://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/Data is stored with Equiom which is hosted in secure servers within the EEAhttps://www.equiomgroup.com/en/privacy-policy/Prospective MembersName and contact informationInformation and documents relating to the services we are providing, including communications with you.Data is stored within Act  which is hosted in secure servers within the EEA https://www.act.com/en-uk/privacy-policy.Data is also stored with Text Anywhere which is hosted within the EEAhttp://www.textanywhere.net/privacy-policy.aspxJob ApplicantsName and contact informationCV and application form.Data is stored in manual records in locked filing cabinets and computer held records are password controlled.Data is also stored within the Indeed database.  For more information go to: https://www.indeed.co.uk/legal#privacyCurrent and Former EmployeesName, date of birth, and contact informationNational insurance number and Unique Tax Reference (UTR)Information relating to your qualifications and experienceInformation relating to performance reviews.Copies of passports or EU IDData is stored on secure EEA-based servers.Data is also stored using Sage Payroll.   https://www.sage.co.uk/uk/hrpayrollhero/privacy-policy.Data is stored with The People’s Pension.  For more information go to:https://thepeoplespension.co.uk/privacy/SuppliersContact detailsBank detailsDescription of the services boughtData is stored on secure UK-based servers.  https://www.sage.co.uk/uk/hrpayrollhero/privacy-policy.Open Competition EntrantsContact DetailsDates of previous visitsData is stored in Intelligent Golf which is hosted in secure servers within the EEAhttps://www.intelligentgolf.co.uk/privacyGreen Fee VisitorsContact DetailsPayment detailsData is stored on secure UK-based servers and also in Intelligent Golf which is hosted in secure servers within the EEAhttps://www.intelligentgolf.co.uk/privacyGolf Day or Event BookingsContact DetailsDates of previous bookingsDescription of the products and services purchase/usedData is stored on secure UK-based servers and also in Intelligent Golf which is hosted in secure servers within the EEAhttps://www.intelligentgolf.co.uk/privacyWe will only retain your personal data for as long as is necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it is collected.Members NewsletterWe use a third-party provider, Mail Chimp, to deliver our members newsletters. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies including clear gifs to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. As a member you can manage what electronic communications you receive from the club and can unsubscribe at any time.Emailing usWe use Transport Layer Security (TLS) to encrypt and protect email traffic in line with government standards. If your email service does not support TLS, you should be aware that any emails we send or receive may not be protected in transit.We will also monitor any emails sent to us, including file attachments, for viruses or malicious software. Please be aware that you have a responsibility to ensure that any email you send is within the bounds of the law.Who has access to your information? We do not sell or rent your personal data or information to any third party or share your information with third parties for their marketing purposes. We will disclose your data or information if required by law, for example by a court order or for the prevention of fraud or other crime.                                                     We may pass your information on to our third-party service providers, agents or subcontractors for the purposes of completing a task or providing services to you on our behalf (for example to manage your subscriptions).  However, we disclose only the personal information necessary to deliver that service and have a contract in place that requires them to keep your information secure and not to use it for their own marketing purposes. Third party services providers who act as data processors on our behalf:Sage provide Payroll and accounting services to MRGC 2013 LTD.  They cannot use the data we hold for their own purposes.The Pension People provide Pension services to MRGC 2013 LTD.  They cannot use the data we hold for their own purposes.Imagination are responsible for the maintenance of Hardware and Operating System for the Club and at times may be required to access our systems for maintenance, upgrade and support servicesIntelligent Golf provide the management system for MRGC 2013 LTD which includes Tee Bookings, Membership, EPOS, Event Management.Equiom provide BACS processing services on behalf of the Club. Transfers outside of the European Economic AreaYour personal information in the European Economic Area (EEA) is protected by data protection laws, but other countries do not necessarily protect your personal information in the same way.  The EEA covers all countries in the EU plus Norway, Liechtenstein and Iceland.  MRGC 2013 LTD uses online tools which host data outside of the EEA.  Prior to selecting such tools, we review their privacy policy and check that the company is signed up to the EU-US Privacy Shield agreement.  Companies who have signed up to this agreement commit to securing personal data in line with EU data protection legislation.Keeping your data secureWhen you give us personal information we take steps to ensure that it’s treated securely and strive to protect it on our internal systems. Your rightsYou have certain rights over the processing of your personal information by MRGC 2013 LTD.  These are:The right to be informed, which is what this privacy policy is forThe right to access the data we hold about youThe right to object to direct marketingThe right to object to processing carried out on the basis of legitimate interestsThe right to erasure (in some circumstances)The right to data portabilityThe right to have your data rectified if it is inaccurateThe right to have your data restricted or blocked from processingHow you can update your informationThe accuracy of your information is important to us.  If you change your contact details or if you want to update any of the information we hold on you, please contact us by email r.greenwood@mill-ride.com or by post at Mill Ride Golf Club, Mill Ride, Ascot, Berkshire, SL5 8LT.  Alternatively, you can telephone us on 01344 891494.How you can access your personal informationYou have the right to ask for a copy of the personal information MRGC 2013 LTD hold relating to you. To do this please contact us by email r.greenwood@mill-ride.com or by post at Mill Ride Golf Club, Mill Ride, Ascot, Berkshire, SL5 8LT.  Alternatively, you can telephone us on 01344 891494.You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our processing of your personal data with the UK’s Information Commissioner’s Office.Changes to this privacy noticeWe keep our privacy notice under regular review. This privacy notice was last updated on 22nd May 2018.Cookies are used throughout this website for tracking session data, and this data is discarded after you leave the website automatically. Persistent cookies may also be used to remember your club selection preference. Created by intelligentgolf version 10.1.2.
Copyright © 2020. Mill Ride Golf Club - Mill Ride, Ascot, Royal County of Berkshire, SL5 8LT, England
